<resources>
    <string name="app_name">EgyptIs</string>
    <string name="Home_title">Home</string>
    <string name="Recommendations_title">Recommendations</string>
    <string name="Details_title">Details</string>
    <string name="Monument_1_name">Sphinx</string>
    <string name="Monument_1_description">The Great Sphinx of Giza is a massive limestone statue with the body of a lion and the head of a Pharaoh, believed to represent King Khafre. It is one of Egypt\'s most iconic symbols, located near the Pyramids of Giza.</string>
    <string name="Monument_1_location">Giza</string>
    <string name="Monument_2_name">Abu Simbel Temple</string>
    <string name="Monument_2_description">This temple complex in southern Egypt was carved into a mountainside during the reign of Pharaoh Ramesses II. It is known for its colossal statues of Ramesses II and his queen, Nefertari, and for being relocated to avoid flooding from Lake Nasser.</string>
    <string name="Monument_2_location">Aswan</string>
    <string name="Monument_3_name">Tutankhamun</string>
    <string name="Monument_3_description">The tomb of King Tutankhamun, one of the most famous Egyptian pharaohs, was discovered in the Valley of the Kings. His nearly intact tomb contained thousands of artifacts, including the famous gold mask, revealing insights into ancient Egypt.</string>
    <string name="Monument_3_location">Luxor</string>
    <string name="Monument_4_name">Dahab</string>
    <string name="Monument_4_description">A laid-back town on the Sinai Peninsula, renowned for its spectacular diving spots like the Blue Hole, along with its relaxed atmosphere, desert surroundings, and windsurfing opportunities.</string>
    <string name="Monument_4_location">South Sinai</string>
    <string name="Monument_5_name">Hurghada</string>
    <string name="Monument_5_description">A major Red Sea resort town in Egypt, known for its vibrant coral reefs, clear waters, and diverse marine life. It attracts tourists for diving, snorkeling, and beach vacations.</string>
    <string name="Monument_5_location">Red Sea</string>
    <string name="Monument_6_name">Sharm El Sheikh</string>
    <string name="Monument_6_description">A popular resort town located on the Sinai Peninsula, known for its stunning beaches, coral reefs, and luxury resorts. It\'s a prime destination for diving, water sports, and relaxation.</string>
    <string name="Monument_6_location">South Sinai</string>
    <string name="Monument_7_name">St. Catherine Church</string>
    <string name="Monument_7_description">Located at the foot of Mount Sinai, this ancient Orthodox Christian monastery is home to one of the oldest continuously operating Christian communities and houses the famous burning bush, believed to be the site where Moses received the Ten Commandments.</string>
    <string name="Monument_7_location">South Sinai</string>
    <string name="Monument_8_name">St. George</string>
    <string name="Monument_8_description">A Greek Orthodox church located in Old Cairo, dedicated to St. George. It\'s known for its beautiful architecture and religious significance to the Coptic community.</string>
    <string name="Monument_8_location">Cairo</string>
    <string name="Monument_9_name">The Hanging Church</string>
    <string name="Monument_9_description">Located in Coptic Cairo, this ancient Coptic Christian church is suspended above the gatehouse of a Roman fortress. Its name comes from its elevated position, and it is one of the oldest churches in Egypt.</string>
    <string name="Monument_9_location">Cairo</string>
    <string name="Monument_10_name">Morsi Abu El Abbas Mosque</string>
    <string name="Monument_10_description">A historic mosque located in Alexandria, known for its beautiful Islamic architecture and the tomb of the famous Egyptian scholar, Morsi Abu El Abbas. It is a popular site for both worshippers and tourists.</string>
    <string name="Monument_10_location">Alexandria</string>
    <string name="Monument_11_name">Muhammad Ali Mosque</string>
    <string name="Monument_11_description">Located in Cairo\'s Citadel, this mosque was built by Muhammad Ali Pasha and is known for its large dome, minarets, and beautiful Ottoman-style architecture. It\'s one of Cairo\'s most important landmarks.</string>
    <string name="Monument_11_location">Cairo</string>
    <string name="Monument_12_name">Salah El Din Mosque</string>
    <string name="Monument_12_description">Situated within the Cairo Citadel, this mosque was built by Salah El-Din (Saladin) and is a significant example of medieval Islamic architecture in Egypt. Its imposing design and location on a hill make it a prominent feature of Cairo\'s skyline.</string>
    <string name="Monument_12_location">Cairo</string>




</resources>